This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
Dear Mom, Dad,
Big Big Brother, Middle Big Brother,
Little Big Brother, Dougie, Henri, Rodney,
Mikey, and Little Sandra, how are you?
I'm doing just fine.
Good morning, I'm sleepy.
Millie, you stayed up all night writing
home to your family again, didn't you?
That's what happens when
you write to each of them
separately down to the last
little niece and nephew.
Daddy!
At least it pays off.
I'm getting rave reviews.
They call my letters the Millie Monthly.
Quality aside, you could have
written several books by now.
What's so weird about that?
Don't you write home?
Uh, yeah, well, I used to write at
first, but it's been a long time.
But I think for most
people, that's normal.
Besides,
what would they say if I told them I
was hanging out with Vash the Stampede?
So you just don't want to write, Meryl?
It's not that I don't
want to write to them.
I guess it sounds pretty lame to
say that I just don't have the time.
Oh, gee, sorry about that.
I must have accidentally
pulled the trigger.
How dare you?
You have a lot of nerve,
you impudent scoundrel.
We're not dumb enough to be scared
by you and your rotten friends.
Oh, yes, it's become clear to me now.
There's a lot of meaning
behind those words, friends.
So stand up with your heads held
high and say what you want to say.
We won't give up our land
no matter what you do to us.
Yeah,
we're not going to take this anymore, and
you can go back and tell that to Morgan.
Did you hear what I said, you old geezers?
Hey, come on now.
My gun went off by mistake.
You know that he mistake my
ass you fat lift golem. What?
What did you say a golem?
Ha
It's so hard my pistols twitching
You have no idea how dangerous that was.
If you make this broomhead mad,
I guarantee he'll leave you with a lot
more than injuries and property damage.
Good God.
You're the ones who are dangerous,
clotheslining him from behind like that.
Meryl, that's a small
sacrifice for a great cause.
I know, that's right.
Way to go, Millie.
That's all you've got to say?
Did you say bodyguards?
Exactly.
If you two were here to protect
us, we'd feel a whole lot safer.
I'm sorry, thanks anyway,
but company regulations strictly forbid
us from taking any part-time jobs.
I understand.
How about you, son?
Are you interested?
Why the hell are you asking him?
The way that he moved when he pretended
us back there, he was exceptionally brave.
You don't say.
Well, it's nothing.
I do the best I can.
Absolutely no way.
How could you ask him?
Don't you know who this
broom head is, mister?
What is it, little lady?
You want the job?
No.
Well, that's great.
Only you would think
of using your position
to help out people who are truly in need.
Well, we have no choice.
I think the situation represents the
category of risk prevention to the T
Why have you decided to come with us mr.
Bash?
Well, I don't know.
I guess something was bothering me.
That's all keep out of this one.
Do you understand me?
Yes, ma 'am
You see that that's our land there
This is incredible!
How is all of this here if
there's no access to a ship?
Amazing!
It's just like a geo-plant!
No, it's not just like it.
This is a geo-plant.
Yes, we believe that a geo-plant ran along
a mineral vein to form this offshoot.
The land value has skyrocketed so high It's
worth as much as a ship 300 yards wide.
That may be, but it couldn't have
gotten this far without a lot of help.
It would have taken a
massive amount of effort.
I remember it clearly.
Twenty years ago it was a tiny bud,
but I couldn't believe my eyes.
Just imagining how we could
raise such lush, beautiful land?
On an arid planet like this, you
have no idea how that kept us going.
That's right.
Our lives, our dreams, and
our hopes are all here.
It is amazing what you've done here,
but what does this have to do
with you hiring bodyguards?
You saw what happened back there in town.
That was not the first time.
The landowner, Morgan,
has been threatening us time and
again to hand over the deed or else.
But that is all going to end tomorrow.
Once we get this deed over to City
Hall, there's nothing he can do.
Hey, guys, it's time to change ships.
Oh, it's freezing out there.
It gets cold at night.
I appreciate all of your help.
Hey, it's no problem.
Since we were little kids, this place
has always been our playground, huh?
Yeah, and we're never gonna give it up.
Besides, we got these two gorgeous
girls tonight to keep us company.
Yeah, I almost wish that
morning didn't have to come.
That reminds me, what
happened to that broom boy?
I thought that for now we
should handle this without him.
I told him to go back
to town in the meantime.
What's this?
A little fight with a boyfriend?
He's not my boyfriend.
Stop it.
I don't even like him.
Let's go, Millie.
We have to go do the rounds now.
Coming!
Huh?
It sure is cold.
Hey, Meryl, is there something wrong?
It's nothing, really.
It's just that I know I've seen the
face in that picture somewhere before.
The only thing is, I
can't seem to place it.
Oh, you mean like a passing fancy?
A passing likeness.
I'm absolutely sure I've
seen that face before.
Who goes there?
Wait! Don't shoot!
Oh no, it's that man!
Well, what a pleasant surprise,
the two of you once again.
You can put your guns
away ladies. Obviously.
I've come here unarmed.
What the hell are you doing here?
I came to try and talk dad out of this.
Morgan means business this time!
Talk dad. Oh.
The picture.
Yep, that's me.
All right the unworthy son now.
Where is he?
What reason could you possibly have
to point a gun at your parents?
It's none of your business,
but if you must know, it's their own
fault for not listening to reason.
I had to do it or they'd
never get the hint.
You face!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Cut it out! Stop that! Millie!
You rotten ingrate, evil and stupid,
good-for-nothing awful son! What?
What's your problem?
What's all the commotion, huh?
Who's fighting out there?
Oh, Badwick.
You mind telling me what in the
hell you think you're doing?
Look at you guys standing there.
You haven't taken care of a damn thing.
Uh, well,
Badwick wanted just one more
chance to persuade his parents,
and we didn't really see any
harm in that, so we just...
He did, did he?
I hired him for his diligence,
but what's the point if he
can't even kill his own parents?
Evidently, I made an error in
judgment having any faith in him.
What do you think you're doing?
That's my car you just destroyed.
Oh well excuse me you probably
did something crooked to get it.
Anyway listen Mr Morgan
my father and little
brother's bail money is
riding on the success of
this little scenario if
you try to take it out
of our pay you're gonna
get yourself flattened.
You're absolutely right
i can appreciate the
value of family i didn't
like that car anyhow.
Great now that that's
settled we'll show you
the strength of our
steel-plated family bonds.
So you decided you're not going
to listen to me, no matter what?
We will not give him the deed.
Your little band of vigilantes isn't going
to be able to help you if you do this.
You'll all be slaughtered.
I think of Morgan as a child who wants a
priceless treasure he knows nothing about.
If not cared for properly, this
land would quickly dry up and die.
Badwick, my son, this
land lives and breathes.
You think land is more
important than your own life?
I don't understand how you
can so willingly continue
to keep sacrificing everything
for this land. Damn you!
Max was right.
He chose to die instead of being
raised by worthless parents.
Huh?
The end.
Almost there!
Ready?
Huh?
Ah?
Yeah, that was really smooth, Mom.
Now, place the next shot
about five yards over there.
Please don't hit the trees.
That wouldn't be right.
I see no point in it.
Jeez, you're ruining all my fun.
Wait, hold on a minute.
Do you have any idea who we are?
Patricia, Tonka-Tee, Jin-Pei, and
the one that I call Miss Kanta.
All together, we are the totally invincible
team of Marilyn, Nebraska and Friends.
What?
You haven't done anything
so don't hog the limelight.
Oh, Mom, you're funny.
Don't be such a stick in the mud.
I sure hope that they're worth
all the money we're paying them.
All right, Mom, come on.
Now let's give Chin Pei a whirl.
What do you say?
Ready, take aim, and fire!
Hey! They're coming!
We gotta get out of here!
What are they doing?
They're not supposed to be here yet!
What do they expect me to do now?
Come on, it's just about showtime!
Um, yeah, right, but...
It figures.
Anyone in the right mind
would just run from them.
That may be solved.
Mom? Dad?
Go ahead and run if you want.
I don't expect you to stay
here and die with us. What?
What are you talking about?
These guys are really serious.
And there's no telling
what they're gonna do.
No!
Leave your minds!
This whole thing has turned into a
real mess, what are we gonna do Meryl?
Meryl?
Damn, we just can't stop him! Huh?
I'm sorry this happened.
You can leave now and
thanks for your help.
I'm so sorry!
Hey, it's all right.
Well, have we come to an
understanding, old man?
Sure.
I understand what a scoundrel
in a pig you really are.
Dad, stop that. Don't worry.
There's no way Morgan's
going to shoot him.
At least not yet, anyway, because the
land would never be his without the deed.
I can't believe that crazy old man.
Why is he doing that?
Are you really that much of an idiot?
He's doing it to save
the land, me, and you.
I can't believe you don't see that.
Huh?
I don't know how you've felt
about your father all these years,
but I'm sure he loves you and is
willing to risk his life for you.
I'm afraid it's a little late
for this lovey-dovey crap.
Unless we give in, Ma,
we're all gonna die here.
This land just eats money.
I'm not sure why it's so important to you,
but it's a burden I'm willing to take on.
Here is a new claim.
A way out of this mess that
is actually worth something.
I'll fill in the amount right now.
All you have to do is tell
me how many zeros you want.
I think my answer's pretty clear.
I'll beat it.
So you want an early death, do you?
Very well.
I'll accommodate you.
What should I do?
Go ahead and kill me.
But the moment you do,
you lose everything.
Can't you see all the
witnesses standing here?
Did you say witnesses?
You've got to be kidding.
I won't leave a soul standing.
My job won't be finished here until
the last man is dead, I assure you.
You can't!
No, Millie! Excuse me,
but didn't your father
ever teach you that it's
wrong to take things that
belong to someone else?
Be careful, little lady!
Are you the tough little helper?
Yes, I am, now you be quiet!
Millie...
You're wasting your time, little lady!
Doesn't matter, you're all
destined to become corpses anyway.
Hmph!
Charming as this is, I'm getting tired.
Let's get this over with.
I don't think so, Mr.
Morgan.
Now that I've heard your gruesome plan,
I'm afraid I can't let you off that easily.
Make even the slightest twitch,
and I'll be all over you and
your sick little band of thugs.
Oh, Meryl, I'm so glad you're here.
I would suggest that next time you
think a little bit more before you act,
Millie, you might live a lot longer.
Right.
Badwick!
Freeze!
I just don't understand any of you.
Why did it have to come to this?
If you had only taken the money and sold
the land, we wouldn't have a problem.
No one would have to die and
we'd all be safe from harm.
I said freeze!
You know, Millie, when you got angry
before, you were right in confronting them.
We should be outraged when
someone threatens their
own parents and do whatever
we can to stop them.
It's extremely important.
Ha ha ha!
What the hell is that?
Are you serious?
Do you honestly believe that you can
turn the tide with those tiny terrangers?
Yeah, want to find out
what I can do with them?
That is if you have the guts and want
to risk taking a chance on the odds.
Go on.
Alright, Morgan, enough!
I got the document!
I got what you've been asking for!
Son, don't do it!
Well done!
Get him now!
I can't! No!
I'll never make it!
But I have to try!
That was really amazing, Meryl!
I did that?
That makes us even now for
your help on the sand steamer.
Hey, is that all the time I get?
Well, then, what do you think of that?
Don't say she didn't warn you.
No one can escape the wrath
of Meryl's Derringers.
Consider yourself fortunate
you're still alive.
Her next targets are going to be your
hearts and brains, and then you're through.
Are you insane?
That was nothing more than a lucky shot.
That gun couldn't possibly have done this.
Oh, could it have?
Nooo!
How could this be?
Our Supergirl technique was
supposed to be totally invincible!
That's enough!
Stop that!
This hit, you blithering coward!
That advance payment I made you
wasn't cheap and I expect results!
So get your act together right
now, do you understand me?
It's alright, Mother.
I'm sure cheap pay is fine.
Everything will be okay.
So go help him.
Or of course, if your son
means that much to you,
why don't you stop throwing him around?
Get off!
I can't handle any more of this.
Let's beat it.
Right.
What's wrong, my dear?
I think I might have pulled something.
It's gonna be all right, dear.
Yes, I'm sure it will, and
no matter what happens,
we have to understand it's what he wants.
We'll just have to trust him.
I don't know how to find the words to
thank you both for what you've done.
Especially you, Miss Merrill.
I want to share something with you from
an old man who raised an idiot son.
Everyone makes their own choices.
Nothing could compare to the love
between a parent and a child.
Your love for them doesn't
have to be a burden.
Instead of worrying about it, do
something more simple, yet very important.
Walk your own path with
your head held high.
Your life is their life.
The fact that you are who you are helps
the people you love to live through you.
I don't know what is so
great about this stupid deed.
This is the real deed?
Yeah.
Now it's in your hands.
Hey hold on a moment, sir?
There seems to be one more claim transfer
in the envelope you need to look at it.
The beneficiary, as
written here, is Badwick.
Isn't that you?
Yes, that's me.
Yikes!
Mira, we're never gonna make it!
I'm sorry, Millie.
This time it was actually my fault
for staying up all night riding.
Mira.
Daryl!
What are you doing?
Dash's bus is getting ready to go!
They're gonna leave without us!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'll see you
next time.
I'll see you in the
middle of the night
People judge people.
Lives are being cut short because
of someone's personal logic.
Mothers, fathers, friends, their entire
past instantly vanishes into thin air.
The question is, should this take
place at the whim of one individual?
A beautiful woman stood before the
corpses of the Roderick thieves.
She told me that she was merely
discarding some useless garbage.
Dominique the Cyclops told me to
just think of it as spring cleaning.